Stefan Mitic

Senior Software Engineer I mitics98@gmail.com

(617) 764-6300

http://www.stefanmitic.com GitHub: Stefan-Mitic

A Software Engineer with 3 years of experience specializing in Agile software development, front-end development, and back-end solutions. Project-based experience with several AI and NLP technologies. A strong history of developing innovative application features to enhance the user experience.

SKILLS

- React, Java, Python, AWS, Dialogflow, MongoDB, NodeJS, Express, MySQL, Git, OpenAI, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Maven, Travis CI, Hadoop, Android SDK, C, .NET C#, Angular 6, R, Vue.
- Technical project management; Cross-functional leadership.
- Team player; Strong communication skills; Continuous learner and adaptive thinker.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior Software Engineer I

10/01/2022 - Present

HubSpot, MA

- Developed the Calling Product to enable inbound call functionality and provide users the ability to receive and accept incoming calls through the Twilio device.
- Diagnosed critical issues efficiently and implemented restructuring of team libraries for improved performance minimizing usage dependencies.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to help research and enhance call quality by introducing new metrics and improving user experience.
- Mentored a new engineer, provided guidance on current system and team processes.

Software Engineer

01/26/2021 - 10/01/2022

HubSpot, MA

- Implemented a new phone number property across HubSpot's infrastructure, improving validation and usability allowing users to create custom phone number properties.
- Enhanced codebase reliability and maintainability by leading typescript migration.
- Played an active role in an Agile environment, contributing to team processes and success.

Software Engineer Intern

05/06/2019 - 08/30/2019

RBC, Ontario

- Collaborated in a team of 6 in an Agile Environment to develop commercial banking retail applications using Angular, Java Spring, and MySQL, streamlining client onboarding.
- Applied industry coding standards and concepts to web application including Backbase.

Software Developer Intern

05/07/2018 - 08/31/2018

SCI Marketview Inc, Ontario

- Implemented Acceptance Test Driven Development in .NET C# for SCI's automotive leasing web application, created a framework to automate Specflow feature files.
- Independently created scripts to automate the creation of tests from existing business rules reducing 4 weeks of QA testing down to 3 days of automated tests.

Algorithm Design Consultant Intern

09/05/2017 - 12/22/2017

Flynxx Inc, Ontario

- Conducted research on airline revenue management and seat inventory processes, created a working copy that illustrates the integration of the Flynxx model with standard seating models.
- Simulated statistical models of demand distribution and calculated potential revenue for airlines if incorporating a relative seating model.

EDUCATION

• University of Toronto Scarborough, Toronto ON

09/06/2016 - 04/30/2020

Candidate for Honours Bachelor of Science